Seen, Galgal Channel, go go go!
Today's project is not over until we run out of Animastard!
Are you ready for this?
We're going to use up all of it together,
I've prepared a few items to help you out, or rather, something to eat together,
Karaage, pancakes, chicken nuggets, chicken, potatoes or salad,
We said so ourselves.
Salad, chicken, and so on.
The ratio of chicken was too much.
So, yeah, yeah. We can't finish without a meeting, so we will do our best.
Now the video, let's start!
This time, I am wearing T-HOLIC's costume.
Let's eat.
Chopsticks are handed out to me.
I'm going to eat.
Do you think the pancakes will fit?
You ordered them.
It's very secure.
I'll be back.
I'll have some.
Absolutely delicious.
Here you go.
Let's eat together.
Okay, pancakes.
Yes, I'll have some.
They're good?
Yeah, it's good.
Do you like it?
What?
It's really good.
Wait, who wants pancakes?
No, we have pancakes.
I think they go well together.
It's like I ate it.
Chicken.
Chicken, please.
It's delicious. I think it goes well with it.
He wants chicken, too.
How nice,
Bon appétit.
Kira pancakes.
That's Kira.
You should try them too. They are so delicious.
It's all about how you can use up all your energy without filling up,
Yeah, it's good.
It's delicious.
It doesn't taste like it.
That doesn't make sense.
It doesn't taste good.
It doesn't mean anything at all.
Let's go to pancakes.
It's like mustard.
It goes well with it.
Not too spicy? Mustard.
It's more of an ingredient than a mustard.
It's a bit strong here.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Let's get this out of here.
We just got a key word.
What?
It's stronger if the ingredients run out before the mustard does.
Toa, you're doing great. He's really putting it on.
I can't eat much chicken.
What?
It's so tough.
Ah...
You must play.
I'll do my best.
Can I have a chicken?
One piece or so.
Isn't this chicken like fried chicken? Yes, it is.
You can have more mustard.
It's fast. It's fast.
The salad is great. I can eat salad. Not at all.
Really? That's the pause.
It's really going away. Already gone?
It's going fast.
Hasn't it gone down at all?
Are you getting faster too, Momochan? Yes, it is.
What? So fast.
Maybe it was a little less at first? Yes, I did.
Of course not. Glare shouldn't say that.
But they put me in a Western-style house after all.
Oh, it's gone.
Then let's have it. Here.
You too, Momochan. It's good. It's good.
This one tastes crunchy. It's not too dry, is it?
No, it's not.
No, it's surprisingly good.
It's kind of sticky. It's sticky.
I thought this was just a project that would suffer,
But I think it might be a lot of fun.
This? Yeah.
You too, Momochan. Yeah.
I thought we were done.
Hey, pancakes are different.
Oh! I turned it.
I wonder if it'll hold.I don't know if I can cut it, this.
Because I turned it. I turned it.
Be careful. It's hidden or something.
I don't think I can get it off.
Just smash it.
That's good, right? Just fluff it up.
Just until I can see it.
It's easy to see. I can see it.
Oh, my God!
What? Isn't it amazing?
Oh, yeah, it's good.
I don't like it. I don't like it.
I'm talking to Limo.
Oh, it's really gone.
Oh, I think it's gone. There's enough for one more.
There's plenty!
There's plenty of room!
Surprisingly.
Delicious.
Something is put on the plate.
He said he had lunch.
But it's not your fault.
Someone didn't tell him. There's another one later, right? I told them not to do it.
No one did.
Let's all go.
There is, but do you want to go? It was like... It wasn't an option.
And even though I told him we were going to Minamiya Diner, he was eating the black monk's food.
I'm eating a lot.
What should we talk about?
Well, fanmin party.
It's changed, finally.
The fan meeting is over.
Thank you for your hard work.
In all, 7 cities.
9 additional shows.
Thoughts.
There was a voice conference and everything.
I wish you could have voiced it.
Yeah.
There's definitely some voices that I hear every time.
It's called "Misakie," the first one.
Before I leave the room, I hear it.
I'm sure I'll hear you say "Misakie.
The last performance was Yuzuha.
Yuzuha's reserve was terrible.
Sometimes it's a game, I'm sure.
Widle Wanson
There was definitely one.
I don't know what it was, but we were having a field day.
It was in the Fami's corner.
It was a field day event.
You know, like, "Guess Who's Doubtful?
It was a game.
If I had to guess who it was, I'd say...
Wylde Wanson.
You heard it somewhere, didn't you?
There you are.
It's not gone.
Not yet.
Well, it's a little tougher from here.
Tough.
It's tough.
You haven't lost the mustard?
It's still down there.
I think it's coming out now.
Anyone who can make it.
There's some left.
Yuzu.
He just eats fries all the time.
He's eating silently the whole time.
Oh!
Minami, you're empty.
All the way?
I'll keep trying.
Always.
I thought you started out small.
Mr. Kuria.
Get out.
Come on, let's go.
There's more.
There's a lot more.
Chemin and Kakerai!
They want you!
Sister! Who's sister?
Oh, it's gone.
Ah, ah, ah...
We bumped into each other today and got...
That's great!
Yay!
Now all we have to do is eat.
Oh!
Finished!
Amazing!
So the honey mustard was a success!
Yay!
Thank you for watching until the end!
Thank you very much!
If you like this video, please subscribe, rate and comment!
Thank you!Please!
Bye bye!